<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Assemblies xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Assembly>
    <Id>1</Id>
    <Name>Flasher Lights</Name>
    <Description>Where you sit</Description>
    <Image>flasherLight.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>28</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>2</Id>
    <Name>Fuel Tank</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>tank.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>31</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>3</Id>
    <Name>Frame</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>frame.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>8</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>4</Id>
    <Name>Front Fork</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>frontFork.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>26</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>5</Id>
    <Name>Front Brake Caliper</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>frntBrakeCaliper.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>17</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>6</Id>
    <Name>Front Master Cylinder</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>front-master-cylinder.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>18</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>7</Id>
    <Name>Front Wheel</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>frntWheel.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>18</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>8</Id>
    <Name>Handle Switch Lever</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>handle-switch-lever.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>26</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>9</Id>
    <Name>Handlebar Cable</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>handlebar-cable.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>16</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>10</Id>
    <Name>Headlight</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>headlight.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>30</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>11</Id>
    <Name>Intake</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>intake.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>28</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>12</Id>
    <Name>Middle Drive Gear</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>middle-drive-gear.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>20</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>13</Id>
    <Name>Oil Cleaner</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>oilCleaner.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>19</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>14</Id>
    <Name>Oil Pump</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>oilPump.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>10</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>15</Id>
    <Name>Pickup Goil Governor</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>pickup-coil-governor.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>12</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>16</Id>
    <Name>Rear Arm Suspension</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>rear-arm-suspension.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>27</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>17</Id>
    <Name>Rear Wheel</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>rearWheel.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>34</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>18</Id>
    <Name>Seat</Name>
    <Description>Black leather bound</Description>
    <Image>seat.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>11</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>19</Id>
    <Name>Shift Cam Fork</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>shift-cam-fork.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>14</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>20</Id>
    <Name>Shift Shaft Pedal</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>shift-shaft-pedal.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>13</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>21</Id>
    <Name>Side Cover Tool</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>side-cover-too.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>30</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>22</Id>
    <Name>Speedometer Tachometer</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>speedometer-tachometer.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>32</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>23</Id>
    <Name>Stand Footrest</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>stand-footrest.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>37</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>24</Id>
    <Name>Starting Cluch</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>starting-clutch.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>24</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>25</Id>
    <Name>Starting Motor</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>starting-motor.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>14</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>26</Id>
    <Name>Steering</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>steering.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>25</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>27</Id>
    <Name>Tachometer Gear</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>tachometer-gear.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>7</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>28</Id>
    <Name>Taillightl</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>tailLight.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>17</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>29</Id>
    <Name>Top End Gasket kit</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image />
    <NoOfParts />
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>30</Id>
    <Name>Transmission</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>trans.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>32</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>31</Id>
    <Name>Valve</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>valve.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>10</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>32</Id>
    <Name>exhaust</Name>
    <Description>routes the hot gasses from the engine after combustion. That’s somewhat critical because if you spent too long breathing those gasses in, you’d probably feel sick pretty quickly (or die). In fact, your standard motorcycle exhaust will house a catalytic converter which helps convert the carbon monoxide expelled from the engine into carbon dioxide which at least makes it slightly more environmentally friendly.</Description>
    <Image>exhaust.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>21</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks>Your engine and exhaust system actually are designed to work together. It gets very technical and the practical application of how it all works includes things like reflected pressure waves. Suffice to say that without an exhaust connected to your engine, you’d be introducing  air directly into the system in the wrong direction  through the exhaust ports (consider how much would enter when riding at speed) which would throw everything out of wack.</HowItWorks>
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>33</Id>
    <Name>Electricl1</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image />
    <NoOfParts />
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>34</Id>
    <Name>Electrical2</Name>
    <Description>elecrtical wiring for ignition</Description>
    <Image>elec1.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>37</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>35</Id>
    <Name>Electrical2</Name>
    <Description>elecrtical wiring for main steering, flashers and lights</Description>
    <Image>elec2.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts />
    <HowItWorks>25</HowItWorks>
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>36</Id>
    <Name>Drive Shaft</Name>
    <Description>A drive shaft, driveshaft, driving shaft, propeller shaft (prop shaft), or Cardan shaft is a mechanical component for transmitting torque and rotation, usually used to connect other components of a drive train that cannot be connected directly because of distance or the need to allow for relative movement between them.</Description>
    <Image>drive-shaft.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>44</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks>The shaft effect, also known as elevator effect or shaft jacking, is a phenomenon occurring in shaft-drive motorcycles. This effect occurs because the acceleration being applied to the rear wheel creates a reactive force on the drive shaft.</HowItWorks>
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>37</Id>
    <Name>Cylinder Head</Name>
    <Description>In an internal combustion engine, the cylinder head (often informally abbreviated to just head) sits above the cylinders on top of the cylinder block. It closes in the top of the cylinder, forming the combustion chamber. This joint is sealed by a head gasket. In most engines, the head also provides space for the passages that feed air and fuel to the cylinder, and that allow the exhaust to escape. The head can also be a place to mount the valves, spark plugs, and fuel injectors.</Description>
    <Image>cylinder-head.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>20</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks>The design of the cylinder head is key to the performance and efficiency of the internal combustion engine, as the shape of the combustion chamber, inlet passages and ports (and to a lesser extent the exhaust) determines a major portion of the volumetric efficiency and compression ratio of the engine.</HowItWorks>
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>38</Id>
    <Name>Cylinder</Name>
    <Description>A cylinder is the central working part of a reciprocating engine or pump, the space in which a piston travels. Multiple cylinders are commonly arranged side by side in a bank, or engine block, which is typically cast from aluminum or cast iron before receiving precision machine work</Description>
    <Image>cylinder.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>8</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>39</Id>
    <Name>Crankshaft Piston</Name>
    <Description>A piston is at the heart of a reciprocating engine. It consists of a moving cylinder of metal with piston rings to achieve an air-tight seal once it is installed within the engine cylinder. The piston is attached via a piston pin to a connecting rod, which in turn is connected to the crankshaft.</Description>
    <Image>crankshaft-piston.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>11</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks>The distance the axis of the crank throws from the axis of the crankshaft determines the piston stroke measurement, and thus engine displacement. A common way to increase the low-speed torque of an engine is to increase the stroke, sometimes known as "shaft-stroking</HowItWorks>
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>40</Id>
    <Name>Crankcase Cover</Name>
    <Description />
    <Image>CRANKCASECOVER.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>35</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>41</Id>
    <Name>Crankcase</Name>
    <Description>A crankcase is the housing for the crankshaft in a reciprocating internal combustion engine. The enclosure forms the largest cavity in the engine and is located below the cylinder(s), which in a multicylinder engine is usually integrated into one or several cylinder blocks.</Description>
    <Image>crankcase.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>49</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>42</Id>
    <Name>Clutch</Name>
    <Description>The job of the clutch is to temporarily disconnect the engine from the transmission.</Description>
    <Image>clutch.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>34</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks>On a motorcycle, we pull in the clutch lever in order to disengage the transmission, then slowly let the clutch lever out in order to engage the transmission gears with the engine — and the bike moves under power.</HowItWorks>
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>43</Id>
    <Name>Carburetor</Name>
    <Description>The throttle (accelerator) linkage does not directly control the flow of liquid fuel. Instead, it actuates carburetor mechanisms which meter the flow of air being pushed into the engine. The speed of this flow, and therefore its pressure, determines the amount of fuel drawn into the airstream.</Description>
    <Image>carb.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>70</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks />
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>44</Id>
    <Name>Camshaft Chain</Name>
    <Description>s job is to open and close the engine’s intake and exhaust valves—like a person inhaling and exhaling. The cam can be in two locations: inboard or over-head</Description>
    <Image>camshaft.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>22</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks>
      The cam can be in two locations: inboard or over-head.
      Inboard cams (seen in Harley-Davidsons and old Triumph Twins) need to reach up to the valves with a system of pushrods and rocker arms, all of which reciprocate back and forth. That’s a lot of metal thrashing around, and it means such engines can’t rev as high, and consequently produce less power.
      Overhead camshafts eliminate most of these extra parts by putting the cam(s) directly over the valves in the cylinder head. The vast majority of modern motorcycle engines and more and more automotive engines use this design.
      SOHC stands for single over-head cam, and it means one shaft (via rockers) opens both the intake and exhaust valves. DOHC is double over-head cam, and means one shaft operates the intake valves while a second controls the exhausts.
      DOHC designs allow the highest engine revs, and are typically seen in sportbikes. But they also often complicate valve-adjustment procedures.
    </HowItWorks>
    <Parts />
  </Assembly>
  <Assembly>
    <Id>45</Id>
    <Name>AC Generator</Name>
    <Description>elecrtical power to run the bike and charge the battery;</Description>
    <Image>acGen.gif</Image>
    <NoOfParts>13</NoOfParts>
    <HowItWorks>The charging system consists of three main components: the battery, which stores electrical energy for use and acts as a buffer for the bike’s electrical system; the alternator, which creates alternating current to run the bike and charge the battery; and the rectifier, or more commonly rectifier/regulator, which changes or rectifies the alternating current produced by the alternator into direct current so it can be stored in the battery and regulates the amount of current produced to prevent overcharging</HowItWorks>
  </Assembly>
</Assemblies>